getacaiberrypure.com 2009-03-22

# BuyPureAcaiBerry.com

**Privacy Policy**

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for all websites owned by Pure Acai Berry Pro 

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information when you visit this site will be treated.  By visiting or using this Site, you agree to the Terms herein stated.  

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When any changes to this Privacy Policy, take place, we will inform you by posting a notice on the home page of this Site  and by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated. Your continued use of the Site after change dates are posted means you have agreed to the new terms. 

How We Collect Your Data

Personal Data: When you fill out a "Free Trial Request", or any equivalent form, and at other times, we ask for information about you, such as your name, age, email, postal address, and phone number, we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18. Anonymous Data: The Website automatically collects IP addresses and usage information from you upon your visit in order to evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the Site on an aggregated basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page, and the length of their visits. 

How We Use Your Information

We may use your personal data in the following ways: 

  * To send you notices about your accounts or transactions with us and to otherwise contact you with information that may be of interest to you.
  * To contact you by phone, email or other methods about our products and services and special offers.
  * To enhance existing features or develop new features products and services.

We may combine the information collected from you on the Website with information that we collect from third parties. 

Sharing Your Data

We may also share your personal data with other third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you as well as service providers for this Site as well as law enforcement agencies if so requested with due process. We may also contact you or share your information in order to enforce our User Agreement or this Privacy Policy, or when we, at sole discretion, believe it necessary or appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets within the WebSite. 

Privacy Choices

If you do not wish us to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes or to notify you about our own products and services and special offers you can: 

Send us us a written request either by email to info@advcancedwellnessresearch.com or via postal mail. When composing request , please include the word "Unsubscribe" in the subject line. You may also click on the following [link](http://www.advancedwellnessresearch.com/unsub.asp) to add your email address directly to our [Unsubscribe list](http://www.advancedwellnessresearch.com/unsub.asp). Please address postal mail requests to: 

**Pure Acai Berry Pro  
ATTN: Unsubscribe  
500 South Pointe Dr. Suite 230  
Miami Beach, FL 33139**

Please note that we do not control the operations of the third parties to whom we have provided your information for marketing purposes. If you do not wish for them to contact you, you will need to notify them of this fact separately.

Sharing Technology

We use various forms of sharing technology to allow you easy, efficient use of the Website, to recognize repeat visitors and to allow you to maximize usage of the Website’s special features.. 

We use clear GIFs, Pixel Tracking, and other tracking devices to follow visitor usage of the Website,recognize users and assess traffic patterns. The data collected through these mechanisms is anonymous, and it is not linked to the personal data you may provide us.

Viewing Ads

When you view an ad for our Website on other sites, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Our advertising company may also use pixel tracking to determine which pages of the Site you visit after viewing our ads. This information is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts. 

Security

Your personal data is stored in highly secure, limited access servers. We maintain strict procedures to protect the security of these servers and your personal data. 

Review and Correction of Personal Data

You can review and update any personal data you have provided by contacting us.

Any revisions or corrections you provide to your personal data will be applicable only to our own website but will not be updated in the records of any educational institutions to which we have already provided your data. If you would like to review and correct the personal data provided to educational institutions, please contact them separately. 

| 

FAQ | Refund and Exchange Policy | Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy | Contact Us

Copyright © 2008 [BUYPUREACAIBERRY.COM](http://www.buypureacaiberry.com/acai-berry-free-trial-offer.html). All Rights Reserved. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease. *As with any weight loss program, proper diet and exercise are an intregal part of achieving results. Pure Acai Berry is not affiliated in any way with Oprah Winfrey, The Oprah Winfrey Show, Rachel Ray, The Rachel Ray Show, ABC news, CNN news and WSJ.com. Oprah Winfrey, The Oprah Winfrey Show, Rachel Ray, The Rachel Ray Show, ABC news, CNN news and WSJ.com are registered trademarks of their respective owners. The individuals shown are paid models, and not necessarily [Pure Acai Berry](http://www.buypureacaiberry.com/acai-berry-best-deals.html) customers These statements have not been reviewed by the Food and Drug Administration.
